This video will explain to you how to make the knot of the cover effect at the bottom of the T-sheet flat.
First, open the T-sheet project file.
We are going to make a knot on the front side of the T-sheet.
Before making a knot, the particles of the board are set to 10.
In addition, the knot is only on one side, so the left and right sides of the front and left sides must be removed first.
Ensure that the 3D window is shown on the surface of the pattern, and the right and left sides of the clear board are on the opposite side.
In the position of the knot at the bottom of the T-sheet, draw a circle with a diameter of 200 mm with the internal tool.
Add a small fixing pin at the bottom.
Open the T-sheet.
In the simulation state, lift the T-sheet from the bottom of the T-sheet.
In the process of lifting, you can pull the T-sheet manually to prevent the position from penetrating.
Close the simulation after removing the opposite side of the T-sheet.
Switch to the T-sheet locking tool.
Select the part of the inner circle.
Come to the 3D window.
Pull the grid of the inner circle out to a certain distance.
Next, enlarge the diameter of the inner circle a little.
It can be enlarged to 210 mm.
The position can be slightly adjusted.
Let the entire circle contain the fixing pin.
Then select the inner circle line and add a elasticity to it.
The intensity of this elasticity is set to 90.
The proportion is set to 5.
Then open the simulation.
After the simulation, the state is like this.
Here is like a rubber band in reality.
The state of binding here.
Delete the fixing pin inside the circle.
Open the simulation.
You can see the reverse on the front.
The part of the inner circle of the board has been tied.
Turn off the simulation.
This state can be presented.
Next, delete the fixing pin of the bottom row.
Open the simulation again.
The simulation process can be adjusted appropriately by pulling with the small hand.
The back can be rearranged.
Then simulate.
You can use the small hand to adjust the shape appropriately.
Finally, improve the quality of the clothing.
After the simulation, the effect of the front knot is presented.
If the board is a little shaky, you can sew the left and right sides of this circle.
Then simulate.
After the simulation is fine, close the simulation.
Finally, you can adjust the body to wear the T-shirt normally.
This T-shirt knot is made.
This T-shirt knot is finished.
This T-shirt knot can be pressed against long elements.
This T-shirt knot is bonus.
Finally, when the soft stone turns black.
Now, the T-shirt is made.